[{"answer": "Worldstar Designs.  This is Colleen", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hi Colleen.  This is Harry from Top Construction", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Worldstar Designs.  This is Colleen", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Hi, Harry.  How are you", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hi Colleen.  This is Harry from Top Construction", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Im doing great.  Thank you.  Did you get my email with the pictures", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Hi, Harry.  How are you", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " No.  I dont think so.  When did you send it", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Im doing great.  Thank you.  Did you get my email with the pictures", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Umm, I sent it yesterday afternoon around 3:00", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " No.  I dont think so.  When did you send it", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " No.  Im sorry.  I didnt receive it.  What email address did you send it to", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Umm, I sent it yesterday afternoon around 3:00", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Lets see.  I sent it to colleen@worldstar.com.  Is that right", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 22, "question": " No.  Im sorry.  I didnt receive it.  What email address did you send it to", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Oh, no.  Actually, we have two Colleens working at the office.  My email i", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Lets see.  I sent it to colleen@worldstar.com.  Is that right", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Darn.  Do you mind if I send it to the right address right now so I can make sur", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Oh, no.  Actually, we have two Colleens working at the office.  My email i", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Sure.  Go ahead.  Ive got my inbox open right now", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Darn.  Do you mind if I send it to the right address right now so I can make sur", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " OK.  Its sent.  Do you see it", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Sure.  Go ahead.  Ive got my inbox open right now", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Got it.  It worked that time", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 35, "question": " OK.  Its sent.  Do you see it", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Can you open the attachments", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Got it.  It worked that time", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Actually, there arent any attachments with the email.  Are you sure you sen", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Can you open the attachments", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Oh, shoot.  I forgot to attach the pictures.   Im sorry.  This is just not my day", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Actually, there arent any attachments with the email.  Are you sure you sen", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " OK.  Dont worry about it.  We all forget the attachments sometimes", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Oh, shoot.  I forgot to attach the pictures.   Im sorry.  This is just not my day", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Thanks.  OK.  Ive sent the attachments.  Can you open the images now", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 46, "question": " OK.  Dont worry about it.  We all forget the attachments sometimes", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " I see the attachments, but when I click on them it says they are a", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Thanks.  OK.  Ive sent the attachments.  Can you open the images now", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " I dont even know.  Im not really good with this computer stuff", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I see the attachments, but when I click on them it says they are a", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Well, since theyre pictures you need to save them as jpegs.  Also, make sur", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 52, "question": " I dont even know.  Im not really good with this computer stuff", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " OK.  Can you hold for a moment while I try to resave them", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Well, since theyre pictures you need to save them as jpegs.  Also, make sur", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 58, "question": " OK.  Can you hold for a moment while I try to resave them", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Thanks.  All right.  I think Ive saved them as the right file type this time.  I", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I got your email.  Thats better!  I can open the attached pictures now", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Thanks.  All right.  I think Ive saved them as the right file type this time.  I", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Finally!  Sorry about that.  Im always having problems with attachments", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 64, "question": " I got your email.  Thats better!  I can open the attached pictures now", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Dont worry about it", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Finally!  Sorry about that.  Im always having problems with attachments", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " So, the pictures are the ones we want you to incorporate into the t-shirt design", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Dont worry about it", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Sure, I can do that", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": " So, the pictures are the ones we want you to incorporate into the t-shirt design", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " How long do you think it will take", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Sure, I can do that", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I think I can email you some design ideas by next Wednesday.  How does tha", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 74, "question": " How long do you think it will take", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Thatd be great", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 78, "question": " I think I can email you some design ideas by next Wednesday.  How does tha", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " OK.  Ill get started on it right away", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Thatd be great", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Thank you.  And sorry again for the email problems", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 80, "question": " OK.  Ill get started on it right away", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Oh, dont worry about it", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Thank you.  And sorry again for the email problems", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " OK.  Talk to you later", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Oh, dont worry about it", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "02-04", "aSentId": 83, "question": " OK.  Talk to you later", "qSentId": 82}]
